RESUME

V.KISHORE KUMAR

No.6 Murugavel Nagar, L.I.C.Colony,K.K.Nagar, Trichy-620021 Cell: 9994581142

Gmail id v .kishorekumar91@gmail.com

Email id Kishore_v91yahoo.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE:

To apply my competency (Knowledge, skills and Attitude) effectively. In order to dedicate and earn customer's delight and to grow and fulfill my life ambition

PERSNOL SKILLS:

Comprehensive problem solving abilities, excellent verbal communication skills, ability to dealwith people diplomatically willingness to learn and to lead a team. Adaptability to any situation and to work with different type of higher officials.

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY:

I am pleased to offer three years of experience within the food and beverage industry. I appreciate the challenges this field offers and I boast a solid work ethic. Furthermore, I have striven to obtain the most relevant qualifications from accredited institutions. I am familiar with the basic concepts of food handling, storage, inventory and customer relations. The desire of this applicant is to encounter a firm which will help me to further hone my skills within a productive environment. I am more than happy to work as a part of a team while my experience allows me to function independently if the need arises.

EXPERIENCE DETAILS:

- Completed In Plant Industrial Exposure Training in Food and Beverage service department in HOTEL KANNAPPA GRAND GARDENIA for the period of 24.62016 to31.12.2016
- ii. Completed On the job training for F & B Production and Service for the period of 10.03.2017 to 13.05.2017 in HOTEL KANNAPPA GRAND GARDENIA
- iii. original penang kayu nasi kandar Malaysia 28.01.2020 to 30.04.2021 2 years experience
- iv. Gopaldaas Jewellers 1 year experience at working Office Admin Executive Purchase Department.

PERSONAL DETAILS:

Name : V.KISHORE KUMAR

Farther Name : R.VENU

Date of Birth : 24.11.1991

Age : 31

Gender : Male

Marital Status : Single

Nationality : Indian

Religion : Hindu

Language Known : Tamil & English

Educational Qualification : 8 pass 10th fail

Education : Diploma Hotel Management

Area of Interest : Food Production

Experience : Food and Beverage service

ENCLOSED DETAILS:

- 1) Course Completion certificate,
- 2) In Plant Industrial Exposure Training certificate
- 3) On the job training certificate
- 4) Malaysia 2 years working
- 5) Gopaldaas Jewellers 1 year work experience

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that the above particulars are true to the fullest of my knowledgeand belief

Date : Your's Faithfully

Place: (V.KISHORE KUMAR)